It has begun. Nighttime and Idol Dialogue Series
We are Waka Yasumori and Tomoo Fujii from Stardust, Ujina and Hinokyu, and Mr. Generation Tada frame.
Please give us your best regards.
Yay!
I brought my friend.
Yes, I did. This is the first time that members of the same group are talking to each other in a series of conversations between a nightclub and an idol!
It's the first time!
Yay!
Miracle.
It's a miracle.
Yes, a miracle. That's why we would like to present this project.
The title is "Looking back on the 8th anniversary of Igirinaru Talk," and the themes are as follows.
Yah!
You don't like it because it's Yatsu, right?
Yes, it is. Today, August 9, we celebrated our 8th anniversary!
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy. Thank you for everything.
It's already been 8 years.
We've grown up. You've grown up.
Thank you.
I'll be back today.
It's a wedding now, isn't it?
Yes, it is. So, in this night and in Idol, we have a project called "My Three Elements",
It's a classic.It's a classic.
Yes, it is. We introduced you, Ujina-san, too.
This time we have prepared 4 keywords each to reflect on the 8th anniversary of Iginari Talk.
We would like to make a post with 8 keywords for both of us combined.
Yay!
Well then, I'd like to introduce the themes right away.
Here are my four themes.
Ta-da!
Oh!
Wow. That's nice.
Then, Miyu, please do it.
Here we go.
Wow!
Yes. Like this.
Surprise!
Yes. I chose these four.
Yes. So, which keywords shall we start with?
The standard one.
Wow!
I made it long.
Yes. It was 50 centimeters.
The "Oichiban Live" is the biggest venue we have once a year, as well as the scale and the live atmosphere.
This year, the first OICHIBANCHI Live is scheduled for December 29 at Pacifico Yokohama. Please come and visit us.
First of all, you started with a live concert for 500 people, didn't you? Historically speaking.
What is it? Where was it?What is it? Where was it?
Where is it?
Okabayashi Bunka Kaikan.
So we went there in December, it was Christmas Day, and succeeded in performing for 500 people,
The next year, 1,000 people,
The next year, 2000 people at the Sunplaza Hall,
Next was the Electron Hall, Miyuki.
Miyuki. 2DAYS.
We did 2DAYS,
We did the first live concert at Tokyo Dome City Hall and so on,
This year is the 8th anniversary at Pacifico Yokohama,
This year is the 8th anniversary of the festival at Pacifico Yokohama, and this year is the first live performance,
They do a lot of things.
I have seen it. I saw a performance where they danced as hard as they could on a bare stage with a capacity of 2,000 people.
There was also a performance with only lighting,
For the first time, there was a director,
The stage set,
What was it?
There were pillows and stuff,
And there were pillows, and the stage direction had a backdrop that came up from the back of the stage,
I was able to grow a lot through the experience of having such a director,
I have grown a lot through those kinds of performances,
It's very deep.
It is very deep.
The images are also very deep.You are really deep in the video and other things you have done so far.
Yes, it is. It is deep.
It's like that.
It was the best live performance.
Then, let's go right.
Yes, let's go.
Let's go.
Number 1. Hi ace.
Let's hear it.
It's a Hiace,
Every time we come to Tokyo, we usually drive the Hiace,
I guess it takes about five hours.
I became good friends with the chair,
My butt and the chair,
I think I'm going to crack soon.
Already cracked.
About 3 days?
I've been driving the Hiace for a long time,
How many years have I driven it?
I'll put it at 8 years.
I've been driving the Hiace for about five years.
I already know where I want to sit,
That's right. And the seating arrangement.Oh yeah. And the seating arrangement.
This girl says it's the girls' seating.
She is showing us the way.
She is sitting in paper hand #2.
Paper hand #2.
She's in charge of funny things, right?
I'm in charge of interesting paper hand No. 2.
I would like to introduce one experiment in this Hiace.
The member was a girl named Kaya Date.
Kaya Date and I, Miui Transfer, were in the second row of the Hiace,
in the second row of seats in the Hiace,
There are three rows, right?
There are three rows.
In the middle.
We were sitting in two seats.
In the parking area.
We're here.
Everyone got off.
Kaya wants to move his seat.
I want to move.
But the aisle is filled with luggage.
He has to carry his costume by himself,
I have suitcases, too.
And their own baggage.We had our own luggage.
One Pack Kanya wanted to go to the front row.
We straddled the seats.
I straddled the seat and came over.
Then from the head,
Oh my God, zoon.
I ran into it,
I fell head first.
When your feet are here and your head is here,
I ended up like this.
This is how it happened.
Kaya, with tears in his eyes, was asking for help,
I got stuck.
That's right.
It was so funny.
We all held Kaya-san's deerhair together,
and pulled it out.
There was an incident.
It was the incident of the hari-ace, which cannot be thrown away.
It is an absolutely necessary topic to talk about Tork-san,
It's an absolutely necessary topic.
It is absolutely necessary.
If I were to stand in Budokan, I would want to talk about it as an MC.
It's so important that I want to talk about it.
It is important.It is important.
So let's move on.
Please do.
You're going to go. You're going to go that far?
Yay.
Thank you for watching.
No, no, no.
Yes, ma'am.
First of all
What do you mean by "no, no"?
I'm sure there are a lot of people.
We've been having a lot of opportunities to come to Tokyo lately.
We have a lot of opportunities to come to Tokyo.
There are 9 of us.
we have to stay in a hotel every single time
even after staying at the hotel.
I have to say, it's just so crazy.
I'm talking about
So we came up with a plan.
Let's rent a house together.
We were talking about renting a house together.
And it's on YouTube.
It's on YouTube.Since it's up there.
Lots of links
Please jump to this one.
What is the name of the house?
No, no, no.
Fumi-chan is the oldest sister.
It's always Okare-san.
That's her.
In the graduation picture.
Like the one who took a break.
Yes, sir.
He named it for me.
Without this house, we'd never have made it to Tokyo.
That's right.
It's an important place for us.
There was an incident recently.
That's right.
My grandfather
Grandpa...
This old man?
I see him a lot.
I've been seeing him a lot lately.
The other day...
I was staying at the house alone.
I took a bath.Take a bath.
I came to the living room.
I looked at the wall.
And there he is.
Like this.
Time stands still, doesn't it?
I'm in the kitchen.
I thought I saw a litter jet in the kitchen.
I rushed to the kitchen.
I picked it up and gave it a swoosh.
It was moving around so much.
You know...
There aren't many people in northeastern Japan.
There's not much to do in Northeast.
It's cold and beautiful.
There's a lot of nature.
That's why I don't think of myself as having a grandpa at home.
I was surprised because I didn't
I was so surprised.
At first I thought it was that...
It's a little goldbug, isn't it?
I thought he was a little goldbug.
It was a real old man.
I was serious.
I called him a bar...I put a bar on it.
It moved around, and after a while.
After a while, it stopped moving.
I was just watching him for a minute.
And then it stopped moving.
He turned himself into the light.
But I didn't have the courage
I didn't have the courage to grab it and handle it.
It was just a little too creepy.
That's why I didn't want to...
I didn't want it in my sight
I threw a tissue from above to hide it
temporarily out of sight.
The next day
The members of the group
All the members came to the office.
And they all said, "Grandpa's here.
They were like, "Are you serious?
At that time, Yuna, a member
Yuna was going to deliver a message.
I was going to deliver it, but she said let's flip through it.
I was wondering if she was really there.
There was a member who could handle it.
He said, "I can grab it.
I said, "Let's flip it.I said let's flip through it.
Yuna said, "Wait a minute, I want to deliver it.
Yuna said something like "I want to deliver.
So we started an insta-live called just Jii-Distribution.
So we started an insta-live called "ji-distribution".
And one of the members
Rine Kitami had a lot of tissues.
I'm going to turn them over one by one.
That's a lot of tissues.
Every time she turned one or two tissues
The members make a lot of noise.
That's right.
And then I took the last one.
And then, to my surprise...
Kitamiri was gone.
Where did she go?
What a surprise!
Everyone who's watching the broadcast is also surprised.
Surprise!
It's like the worst.
I mean, where the hell did he run off to?
They're scared that he might be back, that he might come out again.
I always put it on the floor.
I put it on the floor so she'll know it's over.He says he's done because he's putting it down.
And...
And then the delivery was over.
I was spending my time with my eyes open.
Later, when the manager came to my house
When the manager came to my house
I told him there was a cockroach here.
He said, "There are cockroaches here.
What? I was like...
I looked closer.
When they die...
I didn't know that when they die, they become tiny.
I didn't know that.
It was so tiny.
I've never seen a G as small as this before.
I heard that a G this size had died.
and the manager got rid of it.
There was a G case at my house.
This is also a topic that can't be ignored when talking about
It's a topic that can't be left out when talking about Mr. Faraway.
I hope everyone will take this 8th anniversary as an opportunity
I hope you'll all remember it.
Yes, sir.
That's all for the first half.So that's it for the first half.
We will be back tomorrow with more of this.
What have we met so far?
Ujiran! Star last during the day
Eginari! Tomihaku-san's
Who is Waka Yasumori?
It was Waka Yasumori!
Thank you very much.
See you tomorrow.